hdwallpapersyouneed.com 2014-06-04

# Privacy Policy - HD Wallpapers You Need!

**Cookies**  
Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. 

**Third-Party Advertisers**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

**Personally Identified Information**  
During your visit, we do not collect any personal information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, 

_hdwallpapersyouneed.com_

obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your IP address and browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh, Linux, Windows, for example). The information is used for the purpose of generating reports for our own personal use to enhance future visits to our website. 

**Image copyright**

 _hdwallpapersyouneed.com_

is a free wallpaper website, daily updated and dedicated to people of all ages. All images displayed on the site are provided only for personal use as wallpaper on computers, cell phones and other personal electronic devices. All wallpapers displayed on 

_hdwallpapersyouneed.com_

have been collected from a wide range public internet resources and remain copyrighted their respective owners. If you are the rightful owner of any wallpaper posted here, and object to them being displayed - please [contact us](http://hdwallpapersyouneed.com/contacts/ "Contact Us") and it will be removed immediately. We do not intend to display any copyright protected images, so please do not ask for permissions to use these images in your projects, as we do not own their copyrights. Most of the links of wallpapers sources becoming dead after some time, therefore we do not give dead links to our visitors, so please dont ask for source links, because we dont store them. 

_hdwallpapersyouneed.com_

may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

This policy is effective from January 16th 2013. 

By visiting this website (collectively, including all Content available through the 

_hdwallpapersyouneed.com_

domain name, the "

 _hdwallpapersyouneed.com_

", or "Website"), You signify Your assent to these policy rules. If you do not agree to any of these policy rules, then please do not use the 

_hdwallpapersyouneed.com_

website. 

**Privacy Contact Information**   
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below: 

You might be interested in something new:
